export default [
  {
    question: "Which instrument is a member of the woodwind family?",
    choice1: "Trumpet",
    choice2: "Clarinet",
    choice3: "Violin",
    choice4: "Drums",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these instruments is a member of the percussion family?",
    choice1: "Piano",
    choice2: "Saxophone",
    choice3: "Flute",
    choice4: "Bongo drums",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which stringed instrument is played with a bow?",
    choice1: "Guitar",
    choice2: "Cello",
    choice3: "Trumpet",
    choice4: " Trombone",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary material used to make the body of a classical guitar?",
    choice1: "Plastic",
    choice2: "Metal",
    choice3: "Wood",
    choice4: "Carbon fiber",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which instrument has keys, pedals, and strings and is often used in classical music?",
    choice1: "Harp",
    choice2: "Accordion",
    choice3: "Bagpipes",
    choice4: "Banjo",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "The 'King of Instruments' is a nickname for which musical instrument?",
    choice1: "Trumpet",
    choice2: "Piano",
    choice3: "Organ",
    choice4: "Saxophone",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: " Which brass instrument has the highest pitch?",
    choice1: "Trombone",
    choice2: "French horn",
    choice3: "Tuba",
    choice4: "Trumpet",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: " Which instrument is used as the lead melodic instrument in traditional Indian classical music?",
    choice1: "Sitar",
    choice2: "Tabla",
    choice3: "Bansuri (Indian flute)",
    choice4: "Sarod",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which percussion instrument consists of small metal discs mounted in a circular frame?",
    choice1: "Tambourine",
    choice2: "Maracas",
    choice3: "Djembe",
    choice4: "Conga",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which instrument is known for its unique sliding sound and is often associated with Hawaiian music?",
    choice1: "Ukulele",
    choice2: "Didgeridoo",
    choice3: "Steel guitar",
    choice4: "Bagpipe",
    answer: 3,
  },
];